[theme music playing]
[Diego] Ivy, I saw Grandpa and
Arnaldo with their bodyguards.
The congressman was just
forcing me on Arnaldo.
Ivy, don't let him. I'll watch over you.
I'll do everything I can
to put an end to this.
Why don't we conduct a survey?
Let's find out what
the public really thinks.
[Julio] We all know what
the public thinks, don't we?
That we, the Ardientes,
can still be trusted.
[Arnaldo] Ivy's right.
Better safe than sorry.
[Loring] We won the survey!
Diego's got a shot as governor
of the new Ardiente!
[Arnaldo] Should I get rid of Diego?
[Julio] Can you really kill
your own brother?
I want you to think carefully first.
Let's just say
this will be your initiation.
Through this, I will know
if you're just mad for power,
or if you'll be a wise and good leader.
So, who is my father's killer?
Is it Emilia?
Arnaldo? Or, is it you?
Even though I never got the chance
to marry and have kids,
at least I was given a chance
to be a mother to you.
You complete me. Remember that, okay?
[Emilia] Ivy is just playing you.
Who knows? She's with Diego,
the star of the survey.
What you should do is go to Ivy
to see just who she's flirting with.
The only thing I can promise you
is that nothing will change.
Lily will always be there for you.
-You okay, sir?
-Sir?
-Sir, are you okay?
-I'm fine! Just stay there.
Sir.
-[grunts]
-Sir, calm down.
-Sir, please stop.
-We're sorry.
Sir.
-Sir, I'll help you.
-I said I'm fine!
Stop pestering me!
[grunting]
-Bro, back off.
-Sir, that's enough.
Sir, please stop.
-How much wine did you drink?
-[laughing]
Oh, come on. [laughing]
I'll be fine.
I'll take these off, Nanny.
Thank you, Ivy.
And thank you for everything.
-Go to sleep now.
-[chuckles softly]
Dear.
Come here.
Promise me…
that whatever happens,
you'll always be happy.
I promise.
I love you.
I love you too.
Go to sleep now.
Okay.
[soft music playing]
Morning.
[dark music playing]
Look at the headline.
How did they find out about this?
I was wondering the same thing.
You said you called for a news block--
-I did! I told you I did!
-What is it doing there?!
You were probably too drunk
that you don't even remember
what you did and what you didn't.
-I'll fix this.
-Never mind.
I took care of it.
Front page material?
Damn!
-Good morning.
-What is it?
There's a letter for you from--
-I'm not expecting any--
-You have a letter.
It's from…
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshot]
[dramatic music playing]
[melancholic music playing]
Oh, Diego.
What are you doing here?
Good day, Miss Camia.
Ivy asked me to accompany you here.
I cleaned up a little
and I brought flowers too.
Diego, thank you.
Oh. Let me get that.
[melancholic music playing]
Hon…
I really miss you.
I'm so sorry I didn't come sooner.
[melancholic music playing]
Dante, I promise
your death won't be in vain.
Lily and I will continue what you started.
The Ardientes will go to jail, Dante.
They'll pay for everything…
they've done to the people.
[melancholic music playing]
You can't leave until you
tell me who killed my father.
First, show me the money.
[sinister music playing]
Is this enough for you?
Now, tell me.
Who had my father killed?
[sinister music playing]
Emilia.
Emilia had him killed.
[screams]
I'll kill her!
She needs to pay! [breathing heavily]
Natalie.
If you want to kill Emilia,
you need to plan for it.
Then set the appointment
between me and Emilia.
Tell her somebody wants to meet her.
This should be enough.
[suspenseful music playing]
Just set the damn meeting!
Diego, thank you so much
for coming with me here.
No problem.
You know…
I treat you and Mister Dante
like my real parents.
That's why you shouldn't
call me Mrs. Camia anymore.
Just call me Aunt Camia, okay?
Okay, Aunt Camia.
-Okay, I'll go now.
-Take care.
-You too.
-[phone rings]
Hello?
You know the river Arthur was thrown in?
Okay. I'll go there now.
Aunt Camia, I'll go with you.
Okay, Diego.
Nanny Carlotta?
[Carlotta] I'll be right there, dear.
[phone rings]
Mom?
[suspenseful music playing]
They have?
Okay, Mom. I'll follow you there.
Nanny, I need to leave again.
They found a lead on Arthur's whereabouts.
I'll be back soon.
Okay, dear.
Ivy?
Nanny?
Take care.
[tender music playing]
Thank you.
Bye.
Wait, I'll see you out.
[chuckles]
-Bye, Nanny.
-Bye, dear. Take care!
I'm glad you wore the suit I gave you.
It fits you.
Oh, by the way.
Where are your cufflinks
with your initials?
You should wear that.
You know, this is
a very important meeting.
[phone rings]
Yes?
Mission accomplished?
Until next time, then.
[exhales deeply]
You see, Arnaldo.
This can't go on.
I can't always be around
to fix your mess every time you screw up.
What's going on with you?
You're so obsessed with Miss Aguas
that you can't even
think straight anymore.
[utensils clatter]
Where are you going?
Ivy will be mine,
whether she likes it or not.
[dramatic music playing]
Women can really make men crazy.
Ma'am.
We found the drum open,
but there's no trace of the man
you're looking for.
But we did find this piece of cloth.
There's a big possibility that
Arthur escaped from the drum.
[eerie music playing]
[Arthur moaning]
[breathing heavily]
-[grunting]
-[thud]
[screaming]
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
[hyperventilating]
Calm down.
Oh, no!
She left her phone!
[ominous music playing]
[doorbell rings]
Ivy! [banging]
Goodness! What now?
Ivy!
Yes, Mr. Mayor?
Where's Ivy?
She left, sir. She went out.
-[grunts] Mr. Mayor!
-Ivy!
Mr. Mayor, wait!
-Mr. Mayor, she's not here!
And now you're trespassing!
She's not here?
Ivy isn't here, sir.
[suspenseful music playing]
Then why is her cell phone here?
Mr. Mayor, she left it behi--
-Liar! [smacks]
-[groans]
Ivy!
-Sir!
-[gunshot]
-[Carlotta screams]
[gunshot]
Sir, don't!
Ivy!
Ivy, get down here!
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy!
Ivy, get out of there! Open the door!
Ivy, open the door!
[banging]
[suspenseful music playing]
[ringing]
Ivy. This is your number, right?
[line ringing]
Maybe it's Nanny Carlotta.
I left my phone with her. May I?
-Nanny?
-Ivy…
Ivy, the…
Nanny?
Nanny!
[gasps]
Ivy--
-[dial tone]
-Nanny?
I think something happened
to Nanny Carlotta.
Garcia, take us home. Hurry.
[suspenseful music playing]
[screams]
-[grunts]
-[shatters]
[groaning]
[screams]
[thud]
-[groaning]
-[gasping]
[screams]
-[grunts]
-[choking]
-[gasping]
-[groaning]
[screaming]
[choking]
[sinister music playing]
Mayor, your grandpa wants
to talk to you in his office.
Mayor?
Arnaldo.
Where have you been?
Arnaldo! I'm talking to you.
[tense music playing]
Nanny Carlotta? Nanny?
[screams]
[wailing]
[screaming]
Who did this to you?!
Tell me!?
[wailing]
Who did this?!
[dark music playing]
Who did this to you?!
[Arnaldo] Gather the evidence,
and put them in the car.
We'll burn everything.
After that, put everything
back in its place.
If you mess up, I'll kill you too.
[dark music playing]
[brooding music playing]
Burn this.
Burn it, sir?
Are you deaf or stupid?
Burn it now!
I'm sorry, Mayor. I'll burn it right away.
Arnaldo.
I feel like a broken record
trying to call you.
You've been ignoring me.
Are you really trying to insult me?
No, Grandpa. I didn't hear you.
Liar.
Admit it.
You're playing deaf because
you did something wrong.
[unsettling music playing]
What do you mean?
I heard you canceled
your meeting with our allies.
To top it off,
you didn't show up to
the campaign rally at the plaza.
Now tell me, what the hell
is happening to you?
Why are you neglecting your job?
I had something to take care of.
With who?
Is it Ivy Aguas again?
I'm warning you, Arnaldo.
Don't let that woman be a distraction.
Or else,
I'll have her killed.
We ran into some problems,
Grandpa, but I fixed them.
Like I always do.
You have nothing to worry about.
Excuse me.
We'll see.
Aunt Camia.
I'm sorry, but you need to leave.
The police are coming.
You can't be seen here.
Diego…
I don't think I can leave
Lily in this condition.
Aunt Camia, I'll take care of Ivy.
You need to go home.
Mom, it's okay.
Please take her home.
Keep me posted, okay?
Don't worry. I'll take care of Ivy.
Thank you, Diego.
Mayor, we threw the corpses
of Miss Aguas' bodyguards into the river.
Good.
Make sure you did a clean job
so the police won't find any evidence.
-Yes, Mayor.
-You can go.
[police officer] We can't find
any signs of foul play.
It looks like a case of suicide,
Miss Aguas.
This wasn't suicide. She was murdered.
Maybe she was going through
a financial problem,
or maybe a relationship problem.
-No.
-Are you sure?
Maybe she was hiding something?
Yes, I'm sure.
I was talking to her when
our call suddenly got cut off.
That's why I'm sure she was murdered.
Have you seen the marks on her neck?
It was caused by the cloth
around her neck--
I'm not stupid!
-That's hard to prove, ma'am.
-She was strangled.
You're cops, aren't you?
Why don't you search
every inch of my house
and look for evidence before you
start jumping to conclusions?
[tense music playing]
Umali, what's that? Did you find anything?
No, sir.
I'll keep looking over here.
Okay.
Mayor, our agent wants to talk to you.
Hello?
Hello, Mayor.
I cleaned up the crime scene.
They won't find any evidence.
[exhales deeply]
Good. You'll get a bonus.
I'll get going, Mayor.
Good evening, Arnaldo.
[grunts]
Good evening, Grandpa.
I received a report…
from a very reliable source…
saying that Ivy Aguas'
nanny committed suicide.
Is it true?
I don't know. Why… Why are you asking me?
Well…
Because I know that…
you know everything
that goes on in her life.
Well…
I don't know anything about that.
Arnaldo.
Look at me straight in the eye.
Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
Don't try to fool me.
I invented those tricks.
Now…
Tell me the truth.
What do you know about the death
of Ivy Aguas' sweet old nanny?
I killed her.
[tense music playing]
Ma'am, we couldn't retrieve any
footage from your CCTV cameras.
Are you sure those are all working?
My cameras aren't defective.
I'm sure my CCTV cameras are working fine.
You know what that murderer did?
They wiped the crime scene clean
to make it look like Nanny
Carlotta committed suicide.
If I'm not mistaken,
they also killed my bodyguards.
But, ma'am… If we can't find any evidence,
all your suspicions are useless.
You're the ones who are useless!
You've been here for hours,
but you haven't found a thing!
Get out of my house!
You're all useless! Out! Now!
I want you out of my house!
Just do what she says.
[unsettling music playing]
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid move.
Are you an idiot?
We are not maniacs.
We don't just kill for no reason.
We kill. Yes! We kill!
But for a higher purpose.
And that is to stay in power…
for the sake of this town.
And, most of all…
for our family's sake!
Ever since you entered politics,
I did everything to protect you,
to give you a good reputation.
And, in a snap of a finger,
you threw it all away
for something that's not worth a damn!
Arnaldo, why did you do this?!
I mean… Will this do you any good?
I don't know! I don't know!
I didn't mean to do it!
[snorts]
I lost my temper!
I went there because I learned
Diego's been pursuing Ivy.
And Carlotta was there!
She got in the way and tried to stop me.
She kept pushing me!
The next thing I know,
the bodyguards were there.
And then… she was dead.
She was dead. I… I didn't mean to do it.
I… I didn't.
This is all your fault.
This is your fault for letting
that woman get into your head.
You're ruining your future.
All the perfect plans I laid out for you.
No.
Nothing will be ruined
because I cleaned up my mess.
I made sure that nobody
will find out I killed Carlotta.
Not even Ivy.
She can't find out because
she'll never forgive me,
so I got rid of all the evidence.
Nobody will find out what I did.
I really hope so.
No one will know.
Ivy, I know what you're thinking.
You know who's behind
Miss Carlotta's murder.
The Ardientes.
One of the Ardientes.
Ivy, no matter what happens,
I'll always be here for you.
I'll help you.
[dramatic music playing]
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
Thank goodness you're awake.
I'm Carlotta, by the way.
♪ And many times her eyes
Fought back the tears ♪
♪ And when her youthful world
Was about to fall in ♪
♪ Each time her slender shoulders ♪
♪ Bore the weight of all her fears ♪
♪ And a sorrow no one hears… ♪
-Nanny Carlotta.
-I was so worried about you.
I could not rest without you by my side.
I want to stay here with you.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
♪ Let her dream ♪
♪ For she's a child ♪
♪ Let the rain fall down upon her ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower
Growing wild… ♪
[Carlotta] You know,
even though I never got the chance
to marry and have children,
at least I was given a chance
to be a mother to you.
You complete me, dear.
[Ivy] Thank you for always being there.
-I can do this, right?
-Yes, dear.
[crying]
[Ivy] I won't let the Ardientes hurt you.
You're the only family I have.
-I don't know what I'd do if--
-Calm down.
All that anger won't do you any good.
I won't leave you.
Who did this to you?!
Tell me?!
♪ Let her cry ♪
♪ For she's a lady ♪
♪ Let her dream ♪
♪ For she's a child ♪
♪ Let the rain fall down upon her ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower
Growing wild ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower ♪
♪ Growing wild ♪
[tender music playing]
Diego.
Thank you.
Diego, any updates?
The police haven't found any evidence yet.
But Ivy thinks that the Ardientes
-had something to do with it.
-[scoffs]
I wouldn't be surprised
if that's the case.
How's my daughter?
She's distraught.
She's been quiet.
Were you with her all night?
Diego, thank you.
Thank you so much.
I feel relieved knowing that
you're always there for Lily.
I know you're having a hard time,
but I hope you won't tire of loving her.
Because you're one of the
important people in her life.
I'm always here for Lily.
Ever since we were kids,
I've been by her side.
Thank you, Diego.
[phone rings]
Natalie.
Didn't I tell you not to
call me when I'm at home?
[sighs]
Well…
I'm bored.
Hmm. When are you going
to set the appointment
between me and your lovely wife?
Natalie, listen to me.
It's not the right time
for you to face Emilia yet.
We need to carefully plan this.
Okay. So, what's your plan?
[giggles]
[brooding music playing]
Nanny Carlotta.
Please forgive me for not protecting you.
You didn't deserve to die.
They may have succeeded
in erasing the truth,
but I have the perfect punishment in mind
waiting for the person who killed you.
And they can't erase it
no matter what they do.
[unsettling music playing]
Nanny, help me find
the monster who killed you.
I won't let your killer
roam free, Nanny Carlotta.
I'll find out who that person is
and make them pay.
[unsettling music playing]
-Bye.
-Wait. I'll see you out.
[chuckles]
[Carlotta] Oh, no!
She left her phone!
[doorbell rings]
[unsettling music playing]
[screaming]
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[Arnaldo screaming]
[bleak instrumental playing]
[suspenseful sting]
A-A-T.
Arnaldo.
Ardiente.
Torillo.
What do you have to do
with Nanny Carlotta's death?
[Ivy] I wish I could dream
of Nanny Carlotta,
and that she'd tell me
who did this to her.
I don't trust her.
Ivy's different. She's not like you.
[Emilia] Can you just help me out?
Let's convince Arnaldo
not to go on this trip with Ivy!
-I'll convince him.
-Go on.
What are you doing, Papa?!
[Julio] You mean to tell me not
even a bullet in his head
is going to convince him
to change his mind?!
[Ivy] Mr. Mayor, I want you to choose
which one of these
I should use to kill you.
[theme music playing]